# **Curriculum vitae**

# Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 mm

GitHub 🕥

LinkedIn in

Blog ...

I hold a Master's degree in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce, and I have established a strong foundation in various programming languages. In addition to my programming skills, I have developed a keen interest in the fields of Machine Learning and Quantum Computing (QML). Furthermore, I possess a wealth of experience in successfully launching and overseeing startup ventures.

# **EDUCATION**

Master's in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

# **Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering**

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

#### RESEARCH

An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6<sup>th</sup> National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) – 2021
English version

• Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate – 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)

Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) – 2019 English version

## SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the **second-highest** GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a **GPA of 3.88/4**.

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Machine Learning (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)
- Programming Languages:
  - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
  - ▶ PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
  - **Python:** Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
  - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

О СТО

Enviroble.com

**University College London BaseKX** 

03/2021 - 11/2022 London-UK

**Full Stack Developer** 

cikit.ir

06/2020 - 02/2021 Mashhad-Iran

**Founder** 

Tradeoption.ir

01/2020 - 06/2020 Mashhad-Iran

**Founder** 

Class724.ir

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

05/2017 - 11/2019 Birjand-Iran

**Partner** 

Daneshjooyar.com

**Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan** 

10/2015 - 01/2017 Birjand-Iran

# **FAMILIAR WITH**

System Design AWS DevOps

**Jenkins** 

Github Actions

Git / GitLab

Agile Methodologies

Docker Travis-CI

MongoDB Postgrsql

Microservice Architecture

RabbitMQ

kubernetes

Cassandra

Terraform

# **SKILLS**

Flexibility Collaborative

**Studious** 

Positive Engagement

Initiative Driven

#### **INTERESTS**

Music

Workout

Travel

**Environmental Activities** 

Technology

## **LANGUAGES**

English Professional Arabic Native

Farsi Native